QA has always been kind of broken. And
while AI accelerates code creation, it
also requires a fundamentally different
approach to quality. I've spent decades
building enterprise solutions. And
despite our most robust testing, some
issues always reach production. With AI
generated code, the issues can be even
more subtle and difficult to diagnose.
I'm Jennifer Sand, CEO and co-founder at
Credential, and I'm excited to speak at
AI Native DevCon in New York City on
November 19th. Passing tests isn't
enough. I'll be sharing an
invariant-driven framework that helps AI
agents understand what production ready
actually means. We'll be talking about
what to verify an AI generated code
before testing even begins. Register at
a nativev.io/devcon
and I'll see you in New York City.